Over here.
J-Jotaro! L-Look!
Watch it, Koichi!
Don't get any closer!
Hey, I said look over here.
Is that his Stand?!
J-Jotaro!
H-He's here!
He's taking the jacket!
Good grief.
Of course he comes to
get his suit now…
Our evidence!
Wait!
We can't just blindly pursue it.
This Stand…
Careful… It's gonna blow!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 23
HEART ATTACK, PART 1
CENTIPEDE SHOES
It's a bomb…
It's a bomb Stand!
So this is how
he got Shigechi…
That's why we couldn't
find him anywhere.
He's… He's getting away!
Let him go, Koichi.
Huh? Let him go?
What are you saying?
If we go after him,
we'll be able to catch
a glimpse of the monster
who slayed Reimi and Shigechi!
We carefully observe the situation,
then make our move, Koichi.
Do you hear yourself?
Sorry to say, I never got
a look at his name on that tag.
But considering
the size of that jacket,
I can tell
he's about 175 centimeters tall.
He's an office worker,
and definitely not hitched.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't have brought his jacket in
for a measly button.
He's between 25 and 35,
not to mention pretty damn rich.
That fabric and design,
that's a luxury designer jacket.
Even without a good look at him,
we just narrowed
our target down big time.
Oh, that makes sense…
No way! So we just throw up
our hands and wait?
He's a cold-blooded killer!
It's not a choice, we can't.
That bomb Stand
is somewhere over there.
Huh?! The Stand?
Y-You saw it?
No, but I know it's here.
Slowly we make our way
out the door.
You know? Just hang on a second.
How can you know its location
if you can't see it?
If he were the kind of killer
to up and run after offing
only that shop owner,
there would've been no way
he could've kept killing
for fifteen years.
This bastard leaves
no evidence behind.
Which means he intends
to take us out too.
Wait… Don't you think
you're being a little too careful?
If his Stand isn't here,
our murderer and
evidence could be long gone by now.
Listen, Koichi.
Observing involves
more than just looking.
LOOKING
It means scrutinizing everything.
SCRUTINIZING
You don't just listen,
you concentrate.
LISTEN
CONCENTRATE
Otherwise,
we die here in this room.
I don't think I like his tone…
It's not like Reverb isn't capable.
He's matured a lot.
Maybe Mr. Jotaro just
doesn't take me seriously…
It sure doesn't look like
that bomb Stand is still around.
Then we'd be the chumps,
wouldn't we!
Over here.
I-It was here all along!
I-It'll explode if
I keep touching it!
Star Platinum!
I knocked the shit out of that thing…
and it still managed to
stay in one piece.
It's gonna blow!
Star Platinum! The World!
I prefer not to break a sweat,
so I'll dispose of you
right here and now.
Y-Yes!
You must have stopped time.
Then, it doesn't matter
how much you touch it!
Anyone who dares pursue
Yoshikage Kira
shall perish by explosion.
Once my Deadly Queen's Heart Attack
finds its prey,
it won't stop until it makes its kill.
Holy shit! Even Star Platinum
couldn't destroy it!
It's indestructible…
How the hell!
Get back, Koichi.
It isn't damaged!
Nothing seems to phase
this thing at all!
Get back, Koichi!
Y-You've hit him
so hard you're bleeding,
and it's still totally fine!
Get far away, Koichi!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
What are you doing?!
It'll explode if you touch it!
Get rid of that thing, fast!
Over here.
Good grief. This is definitely a first…
this Stand's resilience is insane.
My confidence is going
to break before it does.
J-Jotaro, at this rate,
he's gonna blow us to smithereens!
You're still way too close.
I'm gonna dismantle
this alarm clock from hell for good.
You gotta listen to me.
Stands controlled from afar
wield only a marginal amount
of power.
The way it charges,
the power of its explosions…
There's no way its user
isn't nearby.
At the very most he's fifteen…
no, ten meters away!
And?
"And"?! It's ten meters!
My Reverb has
a range of fifty meters!
I know I can find that prick!
I told you, Koichi.
Don't go after him.
Your job is to focus on
protecting your own hide with Reverb.
Everything else
is unnecessary.
W-Why?!
Our murderer is no longer close by.
We're dealing with
a long-range Stand.
I've seen enough of these freaks
of nature to know.
Over here.
Its movements are too simple
for a short-range stand.
He's seen enough of them?
But that doesn't make
any sense!
An overwhelmingly powerful
long-range Stand…
The user has to be close by!
So Mr. Jotaro really
doesn't take me seriously
I've matured, too!
I can locate and destroy him!
Distance, ten meters.
There! That's him!
He has the jacket!
I don't get it…
H-He's too faraway.
He's more than fifty meters away…
He keeps walking away.
He's outside Reverb's range!
Th-The bomb Stand is
a long-range Stand?
That can't be!
That kind of power
with a long-range Stand is impossible!
Over here!
W-What? He's charging toward me?!
Now I've got it.
It's drawn to whichever object
it detects is hottest.
That's how a long-range Stand
can be so powerful.
Summon Reverb and
protect yourself!
Stopping time is no use,
you're too far away!
C-Crap!
Reverb is…
fifty meters away with
the killer!
Please forgive me!
Good grief.
Star Platinum! The World!
He attacked the shop owner first
because he was holding
a cup with hot liquid.
It targeted Koichi because…
his agitated state had risen
his body temperature.
If it detects something hotter,
it should go after that.
Time resume.
I was right.
It's drawn to the highest temperature
it can detect.
Thank goodness…
But if body temperature
is enough to set it off,
then fire will make it…
This power…
Huh?!
Mr. Jotaro!
HEART ATTACK
How could I let this happen?
This is all my fault, Mr. Jotaro!
All because I went
after that bastard.
This would've never happened
if he hadn't stopped time and
started a fire to save me!
Wake up, Jotaro!
Jotaro! Jotaro!
That wasn't human flesh exploding!
Over here.
It's gonna kill us!
It's too strong!
It's just like Jotaro said!
If it detects something hotter
than body temperature,
it'll go after that first.
Over here.
Now's my chance to run!
I've got to call Josuke.
He'll make Mr. Jotaro all better!
I have to phone him…
I have to let him know!
Of course… the kitchen!
Plenty of opportunity for fire!
I'll buy some time and
escape out that door.
There's a phone!
W-Wait a sec!
It's not a gas stove!
Why the hell does this house
have an electric stove?!
It'll take forever to warm up!
The oven's electric, too!
W-What can I do…
That's it! There's always
an electric kettle with hot water.
Try and find me now!
It's empty!
Over here.
Wait. It's like Mr. Jotaro said…
carefully observe…
This thing has a weakness!
I never noticed it!
Besides, you're starting
to piss me off.
Why should some punk killer
have the satisfaction of
watching me flee the scene
begging God for mercy?
Shouldn't roles be reversed?
I know I can get out
of this alive.
So why am I standing here
thinking I'd rather be
running to the crapper with
a bad case of the shits?
I had it all wrong.
The one running away like
a scared little bitch…
is you, the murderer!
You're unrelenting in
your pursuit of thermal energy…
But that's also your shortcoming!
Your inability to stop will
be your ultimate undoing!
It's been almost three minutes.
I don't know what has transpired
at that shoe store,
but if there's one thing
I'm certain of,
it's that Heart Attack
has no weaknesses.
It will track down and
destroy its target.
Now, then… With him out of the way,
I need to phone Josuke.
He should be home now…
SIZZLE
He's lost us now.
That "sizzle" should keep you
busy for a while…
Kinda like a donkey chasing
a carrot hanging from a stick
in front of its nose.
That, sir, is your fatal flaw.
Hello, Higashikata residence.
Josuke, it's Koichi! I need help!
Jotaro's hurt bad and,
I hate to say it, but I'm at fault.
Just get here fast!
What?! I need a second
to process!
What the hell's going on!
Just focus on getting here asap.
It finally happened!
We found the murderer!
I'm holding his Stand captive
here now.
You're holding what captive?!
Speak up so I can hear you!
Where are you?
W-What the…?
Ow, hot! I turned this thing off
a while ago,
and now it starts to heat up.
What's with this heap of junk?
How the hell does anybody cook
with this thing?!
Hey! Koichi,
tell me where I can find you!
Over here.
Crap! It's ignoring Reverb's
writing and charging this way!
Koichi, where are you?
Hurry up and tell me, you idiot!
Centipede Shoes! Hurry quick!
Damn, it still has part
of Reverb's tail…
He blew it up!
The damage transferred to me…
That wasn't human flesh exploding.
Over here.
It's at it again!
It's charging me again.
But now I can't use my tail
to transform into writing.
Now what?
How can I fight back?
Reverb Act 2!
What's wrong, Reverb Act 2?!
Act 2!
Where are you, Act 2?!
Why won't you appear?!
Act 2… It got him with his bomb!
It split him completely apart!
N-No, wait…
If it killed him in the blast,
I'd be dead too; I'm the user.
N-Now I remember!
This isn't the first time Reverb
looked like a lifeless shell.
That must mean…
C-Could it be…
BOOOOM
Reverb Act 3!
Um, assuming that is
who you are, sir?
Awaiting orders.
So that means I've matured?!
You're amazing, Act 3!
Awaiting orders.
Er, I'm not exactly familiar with
your capabilities, so… F-For now…
Protect us from harm, Act 3!
Um, I mean keep us safe, please.
You can do that, right?
Command acquired.
DOGYAN
This force!
He's so incredibly fast!
Act 1 and Act 2 can't
even compare!
SNAP
Activating… Reverb Act 3 Freeze!
KERBAM BAM
CRASH
H-Hey, Act 3?!
Formidable indeed. It's no use.
It's no use?!
Our foe is particularly
herculean in strength.
S-H-I-T.
I tried but failed.
You tried but failed?
I meant what I said!
I commanded you to
protect us from harm!
The act of protecting
has been completed.
As ordered, sir.
Over here.
Completed?! Like what?!
You're completely useless!
You haven't made any progress at all!
Over he—
W-What?
This is taking too long.
What's holding Heart Attack back?
W-What the…?
What's happening to my hand…
I released Heart Attack
with my left hand, and now…
Sir, is everything all right?
May I be of assistance?
It's nothing.
Allow me to pay for the cup.
I must be leaving,
the check please.
Th-This is…
M-My left hand… is so heavy!
S-Sir?
I-Impossible! My left hand!
My left hand has…
It feels like a 40 or 50
kilogram weight is pressing against it.
What the hell's happening
over there?
Sir, are you all right?
- Everything's just fine.
- Please, take my hand.
This weight!
What has gotten into you, sir?
I don't understand…
It's been driven into the
pavement and barely moving…
Act 3! What did you do?
What's your ability…
3 Freeze!
"Three" and "free" rhyme, don't they?
Act 3, what is this power?
Why is it barely moving? Tell me.
If there were something
to explain, I would.
It's heavy…
Somehow, something has
made Heart Attack heavy.
Shit. I need to get it back.
I have to go fetch
Heart Attack myself
EPISODE 24
HEART ATTACK, PART 2